# \* Jin Gang \*

### FULL STACK DEVEL OPER

(WEB & MOBILE & BLOCKSHAIN)

- geniusdev0813@gmail.com
- (§) live:.cid.5c18b73dc33affe5
- https://github.com/softwinner813
- **m** 1990-08-13

# SSSSSS

### SKILLS

### Web App Development

#### ....

- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, Yii
- · Vue.js, ReactJS, AngularJS
- NodeJS/Express
- · Python/Django, Flask
- · Ruby On Rails
- C#/ASP.NET

### Mobile App Development

#### ....

- · Android Development
- iOS/iPhone Development
- · Java, Kotlin, Swift, Objective-C
- · Flutter, React Native, Cordova

# Databse Management

#### ....

- · MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, MSSQL
- MongoDB, Oracle

## Blockchain Development

#### ....

- Blockchain, Bitcoin, Ethereum, Solana, Binance Smart Chain
- Dapp, web3.js
- Smart Contract, ERC20, ERC721, ...
- · Remix, Truffle, Hardhat
- Metaverse

#### Service Integration

#### $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

- · Firebase, AWS, Social API
- Payment Gateway Integraion

# **PROFILE**

#### \*\*\*\*

Welcome.

I am passionate professional WEB & MOBILE & Blockchain developer with 8+ years experiences.

I have graduated university here in Ukraine

I will do my best for project to fulfill the demand and build a suscessful product for you with my high full-stack skills,

This is my Goal!

The great philosopher Plato once said, "The beginning is the most important part of the work."

Please feel free to message me and start your project with me.

Thank you and regard

\*\*\*\*\*

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER**

UseLantern (Remote)

2019 - May 2021

- Added new and refactored old website pages and responsive styles for mobile and desktop devices.
- Implemented a full authorization flow using Firebase registration, login, resetting the password, and email confirmation.
- Integrated the Stripe into the main payment flow, subscription plans, and checkout.
- · Completely migrated React to Next.js, deployed to the Firebase.
- · Connect Bitcoin Wallet, Create Token, Manage NFT

### ANDROID DEVELOPER, MOBILE APPS TEAM

Kobo(Remote)

2016 - 2018

- Developed a highly rated eReading app with over 1 million users on a wide variety of Android phones and tablets.
- Contributed to all areas of the code, from Android UI and ePub rendering to SQLite database and server communication.
- Worked as part of a highly collaborative Agile team to deliver regular releases while responding to rapidly changing requirements in a fastpaced environment.
- Designed the architecture of a customized tablet launcher application.

#### BACK-END DEVELOPER

Saritasa

2013 - 2015

- · Created APIs for mobile applications, iOS, and Android.
- Worked with Amazon Web Services, including EC2, SNS, and SQS.
- · Wrote integration and unit tests.
- · Improved the internal web app framework of the company.
- · Worked with Google, Facebook, and Twilio APIs.

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

Specialist degree in Computer Science

2008 - 2012

Krivoy Rog Technical University - Ukraine